<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<ClickToJumpToProblem> ﺔﻠﻜﺸﻣ ﻰﻟﺇ ﻝﺎﻘﺘﻧﻼﻟ ﻂﻐﺿﺍ</ClickToJumpToProblem>




  <AlertNeedStockpile>ﺕﺎﻧﻭﺰﺨﻤﻟﺍ ﺔﺟﺎﺣ</AlertNeedStockpile>
  <AlertNeedStockpileDesc>ﻲﻠﻔﺴﻟﺍ ﺭﺎﺴﻴﻟﺍ ﻲﻓ ﻱﺭﺎﻤﻌﻣ ﺔﻤﺋﺎﻘﻟﺍ ﻖﻃﺎﻨﻤﻟﺍ ﻦﻣ ﻢﺴﻗ ﻲﻓ ﺕﺎﻧﻭﺰﺨﻤﻟﺍ ﺪﺠﺗ \n\n. .ﺀﺎﻴﺷﻷﺍ ﻦﻳﺰﺨﺘﻟ ﻢﻬﻟ ﺔﺒﺴﻨﻟﺎﺑ ﻥﻭﺰﺨﻣ ﻦﻴﻴﻌﺗ .ﺮﺻﺎﻨﻌﻟﺍ ﻦﻳﺰﺨﺘﻟ ﻥﺎﻜﻣ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺔﺟﺎﺣ ﻲﻓ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ.</AlertNeedStockpileDesc>

  <AlertUnforbidStartingResources> ﺩﺭﺍﻮﻤﻟﺍ ﺮﻈﺣ ﺀﺎﻐﻟﺍ</AlertUnforbidStartingResources>
  <AlertUnforbidStartingResourcesDesc> .ﺔﺷﺎﺸﻟﺍ ﻦﻣ ﻲﻠﻔﺴﻟﺍ ﺀﺰﺠﻟﺍ ﻲﻓ ﺮﻈﺣ ﺀﺎﻐﻟﺍ ﺮﻣﻷﺍ ﻢﻬﻟ ﺏﺮﺿﻭ ﺭﺎﻴﺘﺧﺍ ﻖﻳﺮﻃ ﻦﻋ ﻢﻬﻟ ﺮﻈﺣ ﺀﺎﻐﻟﺍ ﺐﺠﻳ ،ﻩﺬﻫ ﺬﺧﺄﺗ ﻥﺄﺑ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻠﻟ ﺡﺎﻤﺴﻠﻟ \n\n. ﺔﻄﻳﺮﺨﻟﺍ ﻰﻠﻋ ﺀﺍﺪﺘﺑﺍ  ﺔﻋﻮﻨﻤﻣ ﺩﺭﺍﻮﻤﻟﺍ</AlertUnforbidStartingResourcesDesc>

  <AlertEquipStartingWeapons>ﺔﺤﻠﺳﻻﺍ ﺰﻴﻬﺠﺗ</AlertEquipStartingWeapons>
  <AlertEquipStartingWeaponsDesc>.ﺢﻠﺴﺘﻳ ﻥﺃ ﺎﻬﻟ ﺪﻳﺮﺗ ﺡﻼﺴﻟﺍ ﻰﻠﻋ ﻦﻤﻳﻻﺍ ﺭﺰﻟﺎﺑ ﺮﻘﻧﺍﻭ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﻞﻛ ﺩﺪﺣ \n\n !ﻢﻫﺪﻳﻭﺰﺘﻟ .ﺔﺤﻠﺳﻷﺍ ﺾﻌﺑ ﻊﻣ ﻥﻭﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﻞﺻﻭ</AlertEquipStartingWeaponsDesc>
  
  <NeedSawmill>ﺮﺷﺎﻨﻤﻟﺍ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺝﺎﺘﺤﺗ</NeedSawmill>
  <NeedSawmillDesc>.ﻲﺋﺎﺑﺮﻬﻛ ﺭﺎﺸﻨﻣ ﻭﺃ ﺔﻳﻭﺪﻳ ﺓﺮﺸﻨﻤﻟﺍ ﺀﺎﻨﺑ \n\n .ﺎﻋﻮﻨﺗ ﺮﺜﻛﺃ ﺐﺸﺨﻟﺍ ﺡﺍﻮﻟﺃ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺭﺎﺠﺷﻷﺍ ﻉﻭﺬﺟ ﻊﻴﻄﻘﺘﻟ ﺓﺮﺸﻨﻤﻟﺍ ﻦﻣ ﻉﻮﻧﺍ ﺾﻌﺑ ﻰﻟﺍ ﺔﺟﺎﺤﺑ ﺖﻨﻛ</NeedSawmillDesc>

  <EquipStartingEquipment>ﻚﺑ ﺔﺻﺎﺨﻟﺍ ﺕﺍﺪﻌﻤﻟﺍ ﺬﺧﺃ</EquipStartingEquipment>
  <EquipStartingEquipmentDesc>.ﺓﺰﻴﻬﺠﺘﻟ ﺪﻳﺮﺗ ﻱﺬﻟﺍ ﺮﺼﻨﻌﻟﺍ ﻕﻮﻓ ﻦﻤﻳﻷﺍ ﺱﻭﺎﻤﻟﺍ ﺭﺰﺑﻭ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﺩﺪﺣ ،ﺪﺣﺍ ﺢﻴﻠﺴﺘﻟ \n\n .ﻚﻃﻮﺒﻫ ﻊﻗﻮﻣ ﻦﻣ ﺎﻫﺬﺧﺃ .ﺔﺤﻠﺳﻷﺍ ﺾﻌﺑ ﻊﻣ ﺖﻄﺒﻫ ﺖﻧﺃ</EquipStartingEquipmentDesc>

  <MentalBreakSoon>ﺎﺒﻳﺮﻗ ﻲﻠﻘﻋ ﻉﺎﻄﻘﻧﺍ</MentalBreakSoon>
  <MentalBreakSoonDesc>.ﺙﺪﺤﻴﺳ ﺔﺌﻴﺳ ﺀﺎﻴﺷﺃ ﻭﺃ ﺎﺒﻳﺮﻗ" ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﻩﺬﻫ ﻦﻴﺴﺤﺗ ﺲﻔﻨﻟﺍ ﻢﻠﻋ  \n{0}\n\n:ﻲﻠﻘﻌﻟﺍ ﻉﺎﻄﻘﻧﺍ ﺩﻮﺟﻭ ﺔﻄﻘﻧ ﻦﻣ ﺏﺮﺘﻘﺗ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﺍﺬﻫ</MentalBreakSoonDesc>

  <MentalBreakImminent>ﺎﻜﻴﺷﻭ ﻲﻠﻘﻋ ﻉﺎﻄﻘﻧﺍ</MentalBreakImminent>
  <MentalBreakImminentDesc>{0}\n\n:ﺔﻈﺤﻟ ﻱﺃ ﻲﻓ ﻲﻠﻘﻌﻟﺍ ﻉﺎﻄﻘﻧﺍ ﺎﻤﺑﺭﻭ ﺔﺟﺮﺣ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﺍﺬﻫ ﺩﺪﺷﻭ</MentalBreakImminentDesc>

  <ColonistNeedsRescue>ﺫﺎﻘﻧﻹﺍ ﺔﺟﺎﺤﺑ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ</ColonistNeedsRescue>
  <ColonistsNeedRescue>ﺫﺎﻘﻧﻹﺍ ﻥﻮﺟﺎﺘﺤﻳ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ</ColonistsNeedRescue>
  <ColonistsNeedRescueDesc>  . ﺫﺎﻘﻧﻹﺍ ﺩﺪﺣﻭ ﺔﻴﺤﻀﻟﺍ ﻰﻠﻋ ﻖﺤﻟﺍ ﻕﻮﻓ ﺮﻘﻧﺍ ﻢﺛ ،ﺮﺧﺁ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﺮﺘﺧﺍ ،ﺫﺎﻘﻧﻺﻟ) \n\n ﺮﻳﺮﺴﻟﺍ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺎﻬﻠﻤﺣﻭ ﻢﻫﺫﺎﻘﻧﻹ ﺮﺧﺁ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﻝﺎﺳﺭﺇ \n{٠}\n\n:ﺽﺭﻷﺍ ﻰﻠﻋ ﻦﻳﺰﺟﺎﻋ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﺀﻻﺆﻫﻭ</ColonistsNeedRescueDesc>

  <BuildARoom>ﺔﻓﺮﻏ ﺀﺎﻨﺑ</BuildARoom>
  <BuildARoomDesc>.ﻥﻮﻌﻴﻄﺘﺴﻳ ﺎﻣﺪﻨﻋ ﻞﻤﻌﻟﺍ ﺍﺬﻬﺑ ﻡﺎﻴﻘﻠﻟ ﺹﺎﺨﻟﺍ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍﻭ ،ﺎﻫﺅﺎﻨﺑ ﻢﺘﻴﺳ ﺀﻲﺷ ﻦﻴﻴﻌﺗ ﺩﺮﺠﻤﺑ .ﺖﻴﻨﺑ ﻲﺘﻟﺍ ﺀﺎﻴﺷﻷﺍ ﺪﻳﺮﺗ ﻱﺬﻟﺍ ﻥﺎﻜﻤﻟﺍ ﻦﻴﻴﻌﺘﻟ ﺔﺷﺎﺸﻟﺍ ﺭﺎﺴﻳ ﻞﻔﺳﺃ ﻲﻓ ﻱﺭﺎﻤﻌﻣ ﺔﻤﺋﺎﻘﻟﺍ ﻡﺪﺨﺘﺳﺍ \n\n.ﺏﺎﺑ ﻊﻣ ﺔﻠﺼﻔﻨﻣ ﺭﺍﺪﺟ ﻊﻄﻗ ﻦﻣ ﺔﻓﺮﻏ ﻒﻟﺄﺘﺗﻭ</BuildARoomDesc>

  <NeedGrowingZone>ﺕﺎﺗﺎﺒﻨﻟﺍ ﻮﻤﻨﻟ ﺔﻘﻄﻨﻣ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺝﺎﺘﺤﺗ</NeedGrowingZone>
  <NeedGrowingZoneDesc>.ﻱﺭﺎﻤﻌﻣ ﺔﻤﺋﺎﻘﻟﺍ ﻝﻼﺧ ﻦﻣ ﺔﺒﺼﺧ ﺔﺑﺮﺗ ﻰﻠﻋ ﻮﻤﻨﻟﺍ ﺔﻘﻄﻨﻣ ﻥﺎﻜﻣ \n\n.ﻮﻤﻨﻟﺍ ﻖﻃﺎﻨﻣ ﻚﻳﺪﻟ ﺪﺟﻮﻳ ﻻ</NeedGrowingZoneDesc>

  <NeedDefenses>ﺕﺎﻋﺎﻓﺪﻟﺍ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺝﺎﺘﺤﺗ</NeedDefenses>
  <NeedDefensesDesc>.ﺔﻴﻋﺎﻓﺩ ﺝﺍﺮﺑﺍ ﺾﻌﺑ ﺀﺎﻨﺑ \n\n.ﺕﺎﻋﺎﻓﺪﻟﺍ ﺩﺍﺪﻋﺇ ﺐﺠﻳ \n\n.ﺎﺒﻳﺮﻗ ﺔﻨﺻﺍﺮﻘﻟﺍ ﺕﺍﺭﺎﻏ ﺃﺪﺒﺗ ﻑﻮﺳﻭ .ﺕﺪﻫﻮﺷ ﺪﻗ ﺎﻤﺑﺭﻭ ﺖﻗﻮﻟﺍ ﺾﻌﺑ ﺬﻨﻣ ﺎﻨﻫ ﺖﻨﻛ</NeedDefensesDesc>

  <NeedDoctor>ﺐﻴﺒﻃ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺝﺎﺘﺤﺗ</NeedDoctor>
  <NeedDoctorDesc>.ﺔﻤﺋﺍﺩ ﺢﺒﺼﺗ ﺪﻗ ﻭ ﺢﻴﺤﺻ ﻞﻜﺸﺑ ﻢﺌﺘﻠﺗ ﻢﻟ ﺡﻭﺮﺠﻟﺍ ﻥﺃ ﻦﻜﻤﻳ ،ﺝﻼﻋ ﻥﻭﺩ ﺖﻛﺮﺗ ﺍﺫﺇ .ﺐﻴﺒﻃ ﻝﺎﻤﻋﺃ ﻉﻮﻨﻟ ﻲﺤﺻ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﻦﻴﻴﻌﺗ \n{٠}\n\n .ﺀﺎﺒﻃﺄﻛ ﻦﻴﻴﻌﺘﻟ ﻲﺤﺻ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﻦﻣ ﻚﻳﺪﻟ ﺪﺟﻮﻳ ﻻ ﻦﻜﻟﻭ ،ﺔﻴﺒﻃ ﺔﻳﺎﻋﺭ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺔﺟﺎﺤﺑ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﺀﻻﺆﻫ   </NeedDoctorDesc>

  <NeedMiner>ﻢﺠﻨﻣ ﻞﻣﺎﻋ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺝﺎﺘﺤﺗ   </NeedMiner>
  <NeedMinerDesc>.ﻢﺟﺎﻨﻤﻟﺍ ﻝﺎﻤﻋﺃ ﻉﻮﻧ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﻦﻴﻴﻌﺗ \n\n.ﻢﺟﺎﻨﻤﻟﺍ ﻝﺎﻤﻋﺃ ﻂﻤﻧ ﻪﻳﺪﻟ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﻻ ﻦﻜﻟﻭ ،ﺐﻴﻘﻨﺘﻠﻟ ﻥﻮﻜﺘﻟ ﺭﻮﺨﺼﻟﺍ ﺾﻌﺑ ﺖﻨﻴﻋ ﺪﻗ ﺖﻨﻛ  </NeedMinerDesc>

  <NeedWarden>ﻥﺎﺠﺴﻟﺍ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺝﺎﺘﺤﺗ</NeedWarden>
  <NeedWardenDesc>.ﻥﺎﺠﺴﻟﺍ ﻝﺎﻤﻋﺃ ﻉﻮﻧ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﻦﻴﻴﻌﺘﺑ ﻢﻗ  \n\n.ﻥﺎﺠﺴﻟﺍ ﻝﺎﻤﻋﺃ ﻂﻤﻧ ﻪﻳﺪﻟ ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻣ ﻻ ﻦﻜﻟﻭ ،ﻦﻴﺠﺳ ﻚﻳﺪﻟ</NeedWardenDesc>

  <LowFood>ﺀﺍﺬﻐﻟﺍ ﺽﺎﻔﺨﻧﺍ</LowFood>
  <LowFoodDesc>.ﺔﻴﺋﺍﺬﻐﻟﺍ ﺩﺍﻮﻤﻟﺍ ﻰﻠﻋ ﻝﻮﺼﺤﻠﻟ ﺾﻌﺑ ﻞﺘﻗ ﻭﺃ ،ﺭﻮﺜﻌﻟﺍﻭ ،ﺀﺍﺮﺷﻭ ،ﺔﻋﺍﺭﺯ  \n\n.ﺮﻴﻄﺧ ﻞﻜﺸﺑ ﺾﻔﺨﻨﻣ ﻮﻫﻭ.ﻥﺯﺎﺨﻤﻟﺍ ﻲﻓ ﺔﻴﺋﺍﺬﻐﻟﺍ ﺩﺍﻮﻤﻟﺍ ﻦﻣ ﺔﻳﺬﻐﺘﻟﺍ ﺔﻤﻴﻗ {٠} ﻂﻘﻓ ﻚﻳﺪﻟ</LowFoodDesc>

  <NeedColonistBeds>ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻠﻟ ﺓﺮﺳﺃ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺝﺎﺘﺤﺗ</NeedColonistBeds>
  <NeedColonistBedsDesc>.ﺭﻮﻔﻟﺍ ﻰﻠﻋ ﺎﻬﻌﺿﻭ ﻦﻜﻤﻳﻭ ﺓﺮﺣ ﻥﻮﻜﺗ ﻡﻮﻨﻟﺍ ﻊﻗﺍﻮﻣﻭ ،ﺩﺭﺍﻮﻤﻟﺍ ﻚﻳﺪﻟ ﺲﻴﻟ ﺍﺫﺇ \n\n.ﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﺮﻳﺮﺳ ﻰﻟﺇ ﻦﻴﺠﺳ ﺮﻳﺮﺳ ﺮﻴﻴﻐﺗ ﻭﺃ ،ﺓﺮﺳﺃ ﻦﻣ ﺪﻳﺰﻤﻟﺍ ﻢﻳﺪﻘﺗ ﺎﻣﺇ \n\n.ﻡﻮﻨﻠﻟ ﻥﺎﻜﻣ ﻰﻟﺇ ﺎﻣ ﺺﺨﺷ ﺮﻘﺘﻔﻳ ﻑﻮﺳ . ﺓﺮﺳﺃ ﻦﻣ ﻚﻳﺪﻟ ﺎﻤﻣﺮﺜﻛﺍ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﻦﻣ ﺪﻳﺰﻤﻟﺍ ﻚﻳﺪﻟ</NeedColonistBedsDesc>

  <Starvation>ﺔﻋﺎﺠﻣ  </Starvation>
  <StarvationDesc>.ﻪﺘﻏﺎﻴﺻ ﻻ ﻢﻬﻧﺍ ﻦﻣ ﺪﻛﺄﺗ ،ﺎﻀﻳﺃ .ﻪﻴﻠﻋ ﻡﺎﻌﻃﻹ ﺔﻴﺋﺍﺬﻐﻟﺍ ﺩﺍﻮﻤﻟﺍ ﺾﻌﺑﻭ ﺔﻴﺋﺍﺬﻐﻟﺍ ﺩﺍﻮﻤﻟﺍ ﻖﺼﻟ ﻉﺯﻮﻣ ﻞﺜﻣ ﺀﺍﺬﻐﻟﺍ ﺭﺪﺼﻣ ﻰﻠﻋ ﻞﺼﺤﺗ ﻥﺍ ﻚﻴﻠﻋ .ﻡﺎﻌﻄﻟﺍ ﺾﻌﺑ ﻢﻬﻟ ﻝﻮﺼﺤﻟﺍ \n{٠}\n\n:ﺎﻋﻮﺟ ﻥﻭﺭﻮﻀﺘﻳ ﻦﻳﺮﻤﻌﺘﺴﻤﻟﺍ ﺀﻻﺆﻫ</StarvationDesc>

  <Exhaustion>Exhaustion</Exhaustion>
  <ExhaustionDesc>These colonists are exhausted and need rest:\n\n{0}\nGet them some rest. They'll need a bed marked for colonist use. Also, make sure they're not drafted.</ExhaustionDesc>

  <NeedFoodHopper>Need food hopper</NeedFoodHopper>
  <NeedFoodHopperDesc>You have a nutrient dispenser with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, paste dispensers must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with raw food.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the dispenser.</NeedFoodHopperDesc>

  <BuildingNeedsPower>يحتاج المبنى للطاقة</BuildingNeedsPower>
  <BuildingsNeedPower>يحتاج المبنى للطاقة</BuildingsNeedPower>
  <BuildingsNeedPowerDesc>These power-using buildings are totally disconnected from all possible power sources:\n\n{0}\nConnect them to a power generator or battery.</BuildingsNeedPowerDesc>
  <AndMore>and more</AndMore>

  <NeedMealSource>Need meal source</NeedMealSource>
  <NeedMealSourceDesc>You have no way of preparing proper meals from raw food.\n\nBuild a nutrient paste dispenser or a cook stove.\n\n(It cannot be in a prison cell, otherwise colonists cannot use it.)</NeedMealSourceDesc>

  <NeedHomeRegion>Need home region</NeedHomeRegion>
  <NeedHomeRegionDesc>You need to define a HOME REGION where your colonists will clean, extinguish fires, and repair things.\n\nDefine a home region using the ZONES section of the ARCHITECT menu.</NeedHomeRegionDesc>

  <NeedBatteries>Need batteries</NeedBatteries>
  <NeedBatteriesDesc>You only have solar generators and no batteries. This means you'll lose power every time the sun goes down.\n\nBuild a battery or two to get you through the night.</NeedBatteriesDesc>

  <NoTradingCapacity>No trading capacity</NoTradingCapacity>
  <NoTradingCapacityDesc>You have no way of trading with passing ships.\n\nBuild a comms console.</NoTradingCapacityDesc>

  <NeedResearchProject>Need research project</NeedResearchProject>
  <NeedResearchProjectDesc>You have the equipment to do research but have not selected a project.\n\nOpen the research menu and select a project.</NeedResearchProjectDesc>

  <NeedDump>Need dump</NeedDump>
  <NeedDumpDesc>You have marked {0} to be hauled, but the colonists have nowhere to take it.\n\nDesignate a stockpile and set its storage settings to accept {0}.</NeedDumpDesc>

  <NeedGrave>Need grave</NeedGrave>
  <NeedGraveDesc>There is a dead body laying on the ground and nowhere for your colonists to take it.\n\nBuild a grave or a dumping zone and set their storage settings.</NeedGraveDesc>

  <ColonistsIdle>{0} colonists idle</ColonistsIdle>
  <ColonistsIdleDesc>These colonists are wandering idly:\n\n{0}\nYou should probably find them something productive to do.</ColonistsIdleDesc>

  <HaltedConstructions>{0} constructions are missing materials</HaltedConstructions>
  <HaltedConstructionsDesc>These constructions are missing materials:\n\n{0}\nYou should probably make required materials available for your colonists.</HaltedConstructionsDesc>

  <TableNeedsChairs>Table needs chairs</TableNeedsChairs>
  <TableNeedsChairsDesc>You have a table with no chairs next to it. Tables are useless unless people can sit at them.</TableNeedsChairsDesc>

  <ColonistNeedsTreatment>Colonist needs treatment</ColonistNeedsTreatment>
  <ColonistNeedsTreatmentDesc>These colonists need medical treatment. Without it, they may die of their wounds, or their wounds may become permanent.\n\n{0}\nTreat them by sending them to a medical bed.\n\n(First, assign a medical bed by selecting it and toggling it into a medical bed. Then, select the wounded colonists and right-click on the medical bed to make them a patient.)</ColonistNeedsTreatmentDesc>

  <ColonistsAwaitingMedicalOperation>{0} colonists await medical operation</ColonistsAwaitingMedicalOperation>
  <ColonistsAwaitingMedicalOperationDesc>These colonists await medical operation:\n\n{0}\nMake sure you have all necessary medical tools and a free doctor available.</ColonistsAwaitingMedicalOperationDesc>

  <PawnsWithLifeThreateningDisease>Severe diseases</PawnsWithLifeThreateningDisease>
  <PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseDesc>These colonists are at risk for death because of severe diseases:\n\n{0}\nMake sure that they get as much doctors care as possible.</PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseDesc>
  <PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseAmputationDesc>These colonists are at risk for death because of severe diseases:\n\n{0}\nIf possible, consider amputating or replacing infected limbs in order to keep colonists alive.</PawnsWithLifeThreateningDiseaseAmputationDesc>

  <!--<AlertAbsentMinded>{0} is lost in thought</AlertAbsentMinded>-->
  
</LanguageData>
