<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<ClickToJumpToProblem>إنتقل إلى المشكلة</ClickToJumpToProblem>

  <NeedSawmill>بحاجة إلى نجارة</NeedSawmill>
  <NeedSawmillDesc>أنت بحاجة إلى نجارة لكي تقطع القطع الخشبية لقطع متعددة الإستخدام.\n\nيمكنك بناء نجارة خشبية أو إلكترونية.</NeedSawmillDesc>
  
  <EquipStartingEquipment>خذ معداتك</EquipStartingEquipment>
  <EquipStartingEquipmentDesc>لقد هبطت مع بعض الأسلحة. خذها من موقع هبوطك.\n\nلتزود مواطنيك بهذه الأسلحة أختر المواطن ومن ثم أنقر بالزر الأيمن على السلاح.</EquipStartingEquipmentDesc>
  
  <MentalBreakSoon>إضطراب نفسي متوقع قريباً</MentalBreakSoon>
  <MentalBreakSoonDesc>هءلاء المواطنين بدأت تظهر عليهم حالات إضطراب نفسي:\n\n{0}\nحسن حالت هؤلاء المواطنين عما قريب قبل أن تتدهور حالتهم.</MentalBreakSoonDesc>

  <MentalBreakImminent>إضطراب نفسي محتم</MentalBreakImminent>
  <MentalBreakImminentDesc>iهؤلاء المواطنين في حالة إضطراب نفسي وهو محتم عما قريب:\n\n{0}</MentalBreakImminentDesc>

  <ColonistNeedsRescue>مواطن يحتاج للإنقاذ</ColonistNeedsRescue>
  <ColonistsNeedRescue>مواطن بحاجة للإنقاذ</ColonistsNeedRescue>
  <ColonistsNeedRescueDesc>  المواطن فقد وعية على الأرض:\n\n{0}\nإرسل مواطن اخر لكي ينقذة.\n\n(لكي تنقذ المواطن اختر مواطن اخر واضغط بزر الفارة الأيمن من المواطن المصاب وأنقذة.</ColonistsNeedRescueDesc>

  <BuildARoom>بحاجة لبناء غرفة</BuildARoom>
  <BuildARoomDesc>لايوجد لديك أي غرف.\n\nابن اربع جدراء وباب لكي تكمل الغرفة.\n\nإستخدم قائمة الهندسة لكي تبني ماتريدد.عندما تضع الأمر للبناء مواطنوك سوف يبدؤون بالبناء فور توفر المعدات. </BuildARoomDesc>

  <NeedGrowingZone>بحاجة لمنطقة زراعية.</NeedGrowingZone>
  <NeedGrowingZoneDesc>لايوجد لديك منطقة زراعية.\n\ضع منطقة زراعية على تربة خصبة بواسطة القائمة المعمارية</NeedGrowingZoneDesc>

  <NeedDefenses>بحاجة لدفاعات</NeedDefenses>
  <NeedDefensesDesc>تواجدت في هذه المنطقة لمدة طويلة. القراصنة سوف يلاحظون تواجدك وهجمون عليك قريباً\n\nجهز دفاعاتك.\n\nإبني بعض المدافع.</NeedDefensesDesc>

  <NeedDoctor>بحاجة لطبيب</NeedDoctor>
  <NeedDoctorDesc>These patients are incapacitated in bed and hungry. They need to be fed, but you have no healthy colonists assigned to the Doctor work type.\n\n{0}\nAssign a healthy colonist to the Doctor work type.</NeedDoctorDesc>

  <NeedMiner>بحاجة إلى عامل منجم</NeedMiner>
  <NeedMinerDesc>You have designated some rocks to be mined, but no colonist has the Mining work type.\n\nAssign a colonist the Mining work type.</NeedMinerDesc>

  <NeedWarden>Need warden</NeedWarden>
  <NeedWardenDesc>You have a prisoner, but no colonist has the Warden work type.\n\nAssign a colonist the Warden work type.</NeedWardenDesc>

  <LowFood>كمية الطعام قليلة</LowFood>
  <LowFoodDesc>You only have {0} nutrition worth of food in storage. This is dangerously low.\n\nGrow, buy, find, or kill some food.</LowFoodDesc>

  <NeedColonistBeds>بحاجة لسرر مستوطنين</NeedColonistBeds>
  <NeedColonistBedsDesc>You have more colonists than you have colonist beds. Someone will lack a place to sleep.\n\nEither make more beds, or change a prisoner bed to a colonist bed.</NeedColonistBedsDesc>

  <Starvation>Starvation</Starvation>
  <StarvationDesc>These colonists are starving:\n\n{0}\nGet them some food. You'll need a food source like a nutrient paste dispenser and some food to feed it. Also, make sure they're not drafted.</StarvationDesc>

  <Exhaustion>Exhaustion</Exhaustion>
  <ExhaustionDesc>These colonists are exhausted and need rest:\n\n{0}\nGet them some rest. They'll need a bed marked for colonist use. Also, make sure they're not drafted.</ExhaustionDesc>

  <NeedFoodHopper>Need food hopper</NeedFoodHopper>
  <NeedFoodHopperDesc>You have a nutrient dispenser with no hopper next to it.\n\nTo work, paste dispensers must draw from an adjacent hopper filled with raw food.\n\nBuild a hopper adjacent to the dispenser.</NeedFoodHopperDesc>

  <BuildingNeedsPower>Building needs power</BuildingNeedsPower>
  <BuildingsNeedPower>Buildings need power</BuildingsNeedPower>
  <BuildingsNeedPowerDesc>These power-using buildings are totally disconnected from all possible power sources:\n\n{0}\nConnect them to a power generator or battery.</BuildingsNeedPowerDesc>
  <AndMore>and more</AndMore>
  
  <NeedMealSource>Need meal source</NeedMealSource>
  <NeedMealSourceDesc>You have no way of producing edible meals.\n\nBuild a nutrient paste dispenser or a cook stove.\n\n(It cannot be in a prison cell, otherwise colonists cannot use it.)</NeedMealSourceDesc>

  <NeedHomeRegion>Need home region</NeedHomeRegion>
  <NeedHomeRegionDesc>You need to define a HOME REGION where your colonists will clean, extinguish fires, and repair things.\n\nDefine a home region using the ZONES section of the ARCHITECT menu.</NeedHomeRegionDesc>

  <NeedBatteries>Need batteries</NeedBatteries>
  <NeedBatteriesDesc>You only have solar generators and no batteries. This means you'll lose power every time the sun goes down.\n\nBuild a battery or two to get you through the night.</NeedBatteriesDesc>

  <NoTradingCapacity>No trading capacity</NoTradingCapacity>
  <NoTradingCapacityDesc>You have no way of trading with passing ships.\n\nBuild a comms console.</NoTradingCapacityDesc>

  <NeedResearchProject>Need research project</NeedResearchProject>
  <NeedResearchProjectDesc>You have the equipment to do research but have not selected a project.\n\nOpen the research menu and select a project.</NeedResearchProjectDesc>

  <NeedDump>Need dump</NeedDump>
  <NeedDumpDesc>You have debris your colonists want to haul, but they have nowhere to take it.\n\nDesignate a stockpile and set its storage settings to accept debris.</NeedDumpDesc>

  <NeedGrave>Need grave</NeedGrave>
  <NeedGraveDesc>There is a dead body laying on the ground and nowhere for your colonists to take it.\n\nBuild a grave or a dumping zone and set their storage settings.</NeedGraveDesc>

  <ColonistsIdle>{0} colonists idle</ColonistsIdle>
  <ColonistsIdleDesc>These colonists are wandering idly:\n\n{0}\nYou should probably find them something productive to do.</ColonistsIdleDesc>
  
  <TableNeedsChairs>Table needs chairs</TableNeedsChairs>
  <TableNeedsChairsDesc>You have a table with no chairs next to it. Tables are useless unless people can sit at them.</TableNeedsChairsDesc>
  
  
  
</LanguageData>
